Hello, this is ELF learning with "What is this?" and "What are these?".
大家好  这里是精灵教育  这是什么  这些是什么
What are these?
这些是什么
They are boots.
是靴子
What is this?
这是什么
It's a cap.
是帽子
What is this?
这是什么
It's a dress.
是裙子
What are these?
这些是什么
They are earmuffs.
是耳套
What are these?
这些是什么
They are glasses.
是眼镜
What are these?
这些是什么
They are gloves.
是手套
What is this?
这是什么
It's a hat.
是帽子
What is this?
这是什么
It's a jacket.
是夹克
What are these?
这些是什么
They are jeans.
是牛仔裤
What are these?
这些是什么
They are leggings.
是打底裤
What are these?
这些是什么
They are mittens.
是连指手套
What are these?
这些是什么
They are pajamas.
是睡衣
What are these?
这些是什么
They are pants.
是短裤
What are these?
这些是什么
They are rain boots.
是雨靴
What is this?
这是什么
It's a scarf.
是围巾
What is this?
这是什么
It's a shirt.
是衬衫
What are these?
这些是什么
They are shoes.
是鞋子
What are these?
这些是什么
They are shorts.
是短裤
What is this?
这是什么
It's a skirt.
是短裙
What are these?
这些是什么
They are socks.
是袜子
What is this?
这是什么
It's a sweater.
是毛衣
What is this?
这是什么
It's a swimsuit.
是泳衣
What is this?
这是什么
It's a t-shirt.
是t恤衫
What are these?
这些是什么
They are underpants.
是内裤
Huh? Two pairs of underpants?
哈  两条内裤
No.
不